<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>other Archives | Forboc</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/category/other/feed/?simply_static_page=2483" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/other/</link>
	<description>Exploring mystic realms, untold secrets, and the shadows between dimensions. Embark on a journey into the enigmatic unknown.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:57:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cropped-forboc-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>other Archives | Forboc</title>
	<link>/category/other/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Descent of the Nameless One</title>
		<link>/the-descent-of-the-nameless-one/</link>
					<comments>/the-descent-of-the-nameless-one/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Forboc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[other]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=386</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the depths of a cavernous realm below all known dimensions, I linger. The world around me—crumbling, dripping, always in shadow—feels both eternally ancient and curiously new. The passages stretch infinitely, ceilings woven with cobwebs and dim luminous fungi, casting feeble cybernetic glows in shades of electric blue and neon green. Every corner carries an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-descent-of-the-nameless-one/">The Descent of the Nameless One</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Forboc</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the depths of a cavernous realm below all known dimensions, I linger. The world around me—crumbling, dripping, always in shadow—feels both eternally ancient and curiously new. The passages stretch infinitely, ceilings woven with cobwebs and dim luminous fungi, casting feeble cybernetic glows in shades of electric blue and neon green. Every corner carries an odor, an ever-present miasma, the stench of eons passed and the weight of ageless waiting.</p>



<p>Above, or so legends whisper in the ceaseless dripping of the cavern&#8217;s tears, there lies another realm—a brighter one. But those tales feel as distant to me as the memories of sunlight to a blind mole, forgotten lore amidst the databanks of my fragmented mind. Books, their pages more like holographic panels, litter my underground sanctum, telling tales of dimensions and existences far beyond this prison. Yet no book, no ancient data reel, speaks of the world above.</p>



<p>Dreams visit me, cyclic in their haunting allure. Within them, I am not merely the prisoner of this abyss, but an entity vast and timeless, a spectral spirit lurking beyond the edges of reality, witnessing epochs come and go. There are memories too—fragmented, corrupted—of being not a singular entity, but a collective, a being of a Great Race beyond the comprehension of most. In this dreamscape, I often wander through cities of gold and shadow, where the buildings pulse like living entities, and the skies are painted with the brushstrokes of an insomniac god.</p>



<p>Yet, as these dreams fade and I awaken, there&#8217;s a lingering sensation—a pull. The underworld tugs at me, deeper and deeper. For there is a descent to be made, a journey further into the chthonic realms. I feel the call, a siren&#8217;s song resonating from the very bowels of this abyss.</p>



<p>It is said that in the furthest depths, beyond even where I dare tread, lies the core of this world—a nexus of power and dark ambition. As I journey deeper, the walls come alive, whispering tales not of ascension, but of a profound descent. A transformation awaits, a morphing from this half-forgotten form to something grander, something terrible.</p>



<p>The passages grow narrower, the air denser. Eldritch runes start to mark the way, their glow pulsating, synchronizing with the beat of my heart. Shadows dance, forming silhouettes of beings—creatures of pure terror and awe. They beckon, guiding me towards my destiny.</p>



<p>And as the weight of this realm presses upon me, I begin to understand. I am to become its guardian, its ruler, a Daemon Lord to watch over this abyssal dominion. The fusion of the memories, dreams, and the ancient power of the underworld mold me, forging an entity of dread and majesty.</p>



<p>In this endless descent, I find not oblivion but purpose. This chthonic realm, with all its terror and splendor, is mine to command, and in its depths, I shall reign eternal.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-descent-of-the-nameless-one/">The Descent of the Nameless One</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Forboc</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-descent-of-the-nameless-one/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
